

PROFILE

A 25 years old student of Computer Science in Business, experienced PM & PMO is looking for an internship in frontend. I am an energetic, communicative person with 7 years of experience in project, event and customer service management. I am looking for opportunities to use my academic experience in coding in a friendly environment.

I have been learning programming for three years:

- HTML & CSS a 4-month program at home.pl
- Frontend a 6-month online course at DEVSTYLE
- HTML, CSS, JS, TypeScript, NODE.JS CodersCamp
- Python 8-month stationary seminar in SDA (including modules from algorithms, databases, frontend and backend)
- Algorithms, databases (SQL), UML object-oriented analysis and design academic knowledge

In my professional work, I took part in application tests, JavaScript and database training. I possess references from employers in London, Wroclaw and Berlin.

CONTACT

- 796 707 205
- K.GOLEBIOWSKA.AIM@GMAIL.COM
- WROCLAW & REMOTE
- (in) LINKEDIN
- GITHUB
- PORTFOLIO

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- GitHub
- Jira & Asana
- Scrum & Agile
- Project Management
- PMO
- Testing
- Django
- Python
- UML
- · Algorithms
- SOL
- Node.js
- React
- ENGLISH B2 / C1 (IELTS)

EXPERIENCE

OPERATION PROJECT MANAGER

PYSZNE.PL - STO2 SP. Z O.O. | AUG 2020 - OCT 2020

I was offered to prolong the contract, but I got covid, that is why I had a break in employment | Poland & Netherlands

OPERATIONS MANAGER & PMO

3YOURMIND SP. Z O.O. | AUG 2019 - OCT 2020

Accounting & finance, events organizer, logistics, hr & administration, front office manager, office management, procurement, project manager | Berlin & Wroclaw

PROJECT MANAGER

Contact with clients, problem-solving, supervision over documentation, sales and marketing activities within the project | Wroclaw

SENIOR ASSISTANT

AMBASSADOR THEATRE GROUP | APR 2016 - OCT 2017

Customer Success Team Leader, problem-solving, maintaining relations with customers in theatre | London

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE IN BUSINESS

WROCLAW UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS | 2017-2022 **WEEKENDS STUDIES**

CULTURAL AND SOCIETY

UNIVERSITY OF WROCLAW | 2017-2021 **INDIVIDUAL STUDIES**